Hello friends, I am Shaandar and a
very warm welcome to all of you
in this video. In this video, I am going to talk to you
about the stock of ICICI Group, where a
significant decline has been seen in the last few days.
Yes, I am going to talk to you
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance share.
Here we will try to attack the chart of the last few days. So
subscribe to it by
subscribing to that subscribe report. The
decline that has been
seen here in the last few days and this should be
used here, try to talk about it. It was
subscribed. A
collection of around 84 deliveries was
seen here. The stop loss on gas at 1315 was
very big, the character of ₹13100 was
launched and it was
trading at ₹139195 paise in the stock exchange till 12:00 in the day. But by
subscribing to the subscribe button here, a big announcement is
expected. After that,
if anyone
subscribes here, if we go here, the
subscribe
delivery report is seen coming.  During the
habit of last January month, while
talking at home, it is important that you will
see that the youth market has been in the market since
January 11, but last
subscribe to the channel, subscribe to the
subscribe, there were lakh 39 thousand, nine lakh 77 thousand,
here the villages used to be normal but
here a little decline was seen in Baghwa subscribe
on 13th, there is a delivery percentage of 12%, on
27th January here the
delivery percentage was 60%, on 25th January also you will
see almost 50%, on 22nd January Clerk
70%, 12% place a delivery percentage of around 7.9 percent, on
which day of January it
was 30 percent, at least on the middle date and here
if you subscribe
try to place it here,
try to compare it in the help chart,
what kind of
indications the chart is giving you, you will see that there was a
decline in March and after that it remained
till November, subscribe and 11:00
subscribe the market also by the results,
subscribe subscribe
here  But the recent low was around 1420 1428,
it was also broken and going below it, a
local level of up to ₹13100 was placed here, so
₹13100 would be supported, it was believed
that it could take a stop important,
but it broke it here, so
here now if you see it at the remedy level
also, then let it be clear, on this channel you have
seen that very strong
questions, how is the message reading here, the
signal line, we have seen that the line which is the remedy
line, also has a very big gap,
so till this reversal side is
seen coming here,
you will see a special recovery in this topic, as long as there was
a phase of it here, but we will
try to see it, subscribe in this way so that
you try to prepare for it, so much
more soda, you got to see only do
not do, here
you saw a decline around till it went up to 1617, it was
loose and
if you see many years before that, then  You will
see it from the bottom around the language of 30,
this much was required in 2018, so let's
subscribe here and if anything like this happens then
look here and subscribe from here,
you will get three subscriptions from above here,
then you are getting it at a discount of 20 per cent,
so it can be a very good valuation
where you can do a democratic activation,
in its fourth you will see that
it was listed somewhere and
six and a half inches were around Rs 700 and
from there it is trying to double by covering the stop,
so you will get to see this struggle here also
and the important thing that should be said
above is the
balance sheet of any company,
subscribe, so you should see here the profit of the company
continuously
in December this year as compared to last year and
subscribe and subscribe
subscribe but if you try to look here,
if you try to understand the basic GPS of this company, then
if you look at the trend from 2016 to 2030, then there is a
good CR which is called growth.
You can see it here,
in March 2016, GPS Jyoti company had
3065 Jyoti, which increased by 22% by March 2017,
you need to subscribe here and
after that when you subscribe here, then
within the first nine months, you will
try to unite the subscribers by informing them about your surroundings, you
can get Rs. 32 subscribe here, so
subscribe, latest subscribe,
now let's talk about f5, then you have 28.4 1.6
subscribe, so here, if
you have any problem in any way, then subscribe to it and if you
find it there, then
click there and subscribe,
if you think that if
you want to take stock between 10 days, 15 days and you get this
film, then write about it to us,
but if you are definitely relying on one year, two years, 3 years,
5 years, then
definitely it has the courage to double your money after three years, four years,
that war
subscribe  If it is continuously increasing here, then there is
hope of subscribing within the next two-three years. So friends,
how many subscribers did you get?
Friends, if you liked it, then like, share,
subscribe
and tell us.